

Serhii Ikin

Front end Developer

Summary

I had a wonderful experience taking courses at Hillel IT School. During school, I taught html, css, js, so that at the end of the course, I was a person who applied for the position of front end developer. What I love most in this profession is to look at the result of my work, it inspires me to do it better and develop in this field.

000	+~	a+ a	
Con	Ild	CLS	

Good Skills

Skills in development

Kibæk, Danmark

Html

Js

+4550246519

Css

+4550246519 (Телеграм)

Scss

messileonl@gmail.com

Figma

https://www.linkedin.com/in/serhii-ikin-danmark-608054227/

VS Code

https://serhiiikin.github.io/Portfolio/SerhiilkinPortfolio/

Languages Spoken

English (A2,Intermediate)

Danish (B1,Upper Intermediate)

Work Experience

Service work

- · Hookah man
- · 5 years, 2010-2015
- · Doker Pub
- · Hookah services

Work in the field of transport

- Taxi driver
- 6 months, 2015-2016

Service work

- Hookah man
- · 6 months, 2016-2017
- · Jaguar
- · Hookah services

Work in the field of agriculture

- · Pig farm worker
- Denmark
- 4.5 years, 2017 2021

Education

- National University of Bioresources and Nature Management
- · Faculty of Information Technology
- 2008 2014
- Master

Additional Education, Courses

· Kypc Hillel, Front-end Basis

Additional Education, Languages

· Danish school, Danish language, 2.5 years